Isn't my cat adorable?
She died recently. She lived for 12 years.
I cried more for her
than when my husband died.
I felt heartless, like a terrible person.
Which made the depression worse.
I don't think tears are a measure of sadness.
Perhaps it hurt you more
not a waste of a cat,
but coming to terms with her husband's death.
You're right.
I still can't believe he's gone.
I have the impression
that he wasn't back from work yet.
I keep expecting
that he will come and say: "I am back."
I'm afraid that if I cry,
this will all become reality.
Do you have another family?
It helps in times like these
being around other people.
Honestly, I have no contact with them.
But recently my children
they visit me with their grandchildren,
thinking I'm lonely.
And yet it's irritating...
No, that's a bad word.
I don't know how to behave around them.
Even in the family
Building relationships takes practice.
Exercise…
BOSS KENJI GAVE ME YOUR NUMBER.
SORRY I'M LATE.
YOU FORGOT YOUR COAT.
I'M SORRY I DIDN'T COME
AND I'M RESPONDING SO LATE.
HIRO
Yes?
Hello?
We were supposed to meet at Cielo on Valentine's Day.
Yes.
I know.
Sorry for all these messages.
I still have the coat you left behind.
If you don't mind,
I would like to come for him.
Would you have time on Wednesday at noon?
Yes.
So let's meet on Wednesday at 12.
In Cielo.
All right.
What am I thinking? I can't do it!
What an idiot I am!
PACAN
Yes?
You immediately look grumpy.
What is it about? I'm off today.
Well…
I was wondering
Would you like to exercise tomorrow?
Exercise?
Maybe we can go for lunch?
What?
We'd better eat separately.
There is a restaurant
which I'm curious about.
I finally managed to book a table.
His name is Cielo.
Cielo?
- I'll hang up if you don't want to.
- NO!
Sounds great.
Let there be Cielo!
Yes, let's practice!
ROMANTICS ANONYMOUS
EPISODE 4
SWEET CHERRY BLOSSOM
Good morning.
Would you like to order?
I'd like an omakase tasting.
Is it the same for you?
- That's all.
- Of course.
Thank you.
True?
What do you mean by that?
Don't you feel comfortable around me?
I am the only face in the world
that you can look at directly.
Yes, that doesn't mean
that I want to look at her.
So imagine a man
whom you like.
Sorry.
I need to use the toilet.
I don't even give a presentation.
Why am I sweating so much?
Can I
exercise again?
Bright.
Go ahead.
Sorry.
What am I doing?
Sorry about that.
I thought you left.
Of course not.
You keep disappearing somewhere.
Well... I have my reasons.
Mr. Fujiwara.
- Sorry.
- You'll forgive me.
- All right.
- I met with your father.
- What?
Good morning.
This is Mr. Sasaki from Quick Mart Holdings.
Nice to meet you. I'm Sosuke Fujiwara
from Futago Sweets.
Sasaki.
Nice to meet you.
Mutually.
Currently working
as my assistant in The Savior…
Mr. Sasaki.
- Thank you for meeting.
- Mutually.
Sorry.
Thank you very much.
Sorry. Did I mess up?
Whatever. I appreciate it.
Who would have thought that a shared meal would be possible
will it be so difficult for us?
I know.
Who would like to go on a date
with someone like me?
Well…
If you like someone,
it wouldn't matter, right?
Just so-so is enough
We'll sit quietly.
Maybe, but…
But it's too difficult.
If, unlike you,
he would be a nice handsome guy
with a pleasant scent,
I would be very nervous.
What?
Wait a minute.
So compared to a guy,
whom you like,
I'm ugly
unpleasant,
and I stink?
Of course.
I don't stink at all!
Maybe a little.
What?
I don't stink. Mercy.
Maybe you too
doesn't know everything about this person.
Observing it from a distance may vary
from meeting him in person.
Is that what you think?
Oh my?
You've got something here.
Here.
Right here.
Already.
Yep, that's right.
I'm sorry, are you okay?
Absolutely…
it's not okay.
It's not easy at all.
Doesn't this sound like a dating scene
from some romance?
You leave behind an elegant restaurant
and you eat burgers in the car.
But for some reason
they taste even better.
It seems like it's just you two
alone in the world.
It's not like that. Don't stretch the truth.
Before you knew it
you fell in love with her.
What?
She's already fallen in love with someone else.
That's why we exercise.
I really hope
that he will be with this person.
So ro love triangle?
Hey.
This series is getting exciting!
"If our liqueur is necessary,
I would like to meet the new president.
It sounds polite, but it's actually a threat.
What are we doing?
Does it have to be me?
Naoko Hosen.
Proprietress.
Oh boy.
Sorry to disturb you.
I just got this letter.
What is it about?
What can you tell me?
about Gabriel Blossom?
Apparently it's difficult to get along with their boss.
She's raw and intimidating
and choosing business partners,
he's mangling like he's at a job interview.
I only heard about her from Kenji's boss.
If her questions are not answered,
will not sign the contract.
It's like a job interview.
Asks about history, geography of the world,
and even related matters
with environmental protection.
Don't worry.
Mr. Fujiwara graduated
prestigious university.
Does it have to be Gabriel Blossom liqueur?
Yes.
I see. Thank you.
CIELO At 12.00.
Boss Kenji,
Wish me luck.
I will try to be brave.
TABLE MANNERS FOR ADULTS
The only natural water liqueur in Tokyo,
produced since 1965…
YOU WILL GO WITH ME TOMORROW
TO GABRIEL BLOSSOM?
YOU ARE SINGLE, RIGHT?
NO. I ALREADY HAVE PLANS.
IT WAS COLD.
Nice color.
So bright.
I had a skirt around here somewhere.
I wondered if I would ever wear it.
This?
Is this?
- Welcome.
- Reservation in the name of Takada.
We've been waiting for you. This way.
What are you doing?
Mr. Fujiwara?
Please come with me.
I'm listening?
Let's go to Gabriel Blossom together.
I said I wouldn't go.
You're free, right?
NO. I have plans.
Please get in!
What?
You're stopping traffic.
Faster!
All right!
You can't drag me along like this.
Sorry. I couldn't go there alone.
And I can't ask anyone else.
- What about Boss Motomi?
- It scares me.
- And your secretary?
- At the headquarters.
Why today?
You don't want to help the Savior?
I want to, but why today?
Is it really more important
than the Rainbow Palette crisis?
Ssagaji.
- What?
- Please stop.
Should I go?
I could cancel a meeting over the phone,
but I already posted it once,
so I feel terrible.
I know I'm asking a lot...
Well…
I would step into your personal life,
so I can't.
I can only ask you.
Please, doctor.
I just have to say hello
and take him away, right?
What is he like? How will I recognize him?
No problem at all.
He's handsome
and it probably smells wonderful
even without a shower for several days.
Yes.
It's rare to find people like him,
so you will recognize him immediately.
Your heart seems to be beginning
open for me, Darth Vader.
As a thank you for showing your face
I'll go there instead of you.
Really? Thank you very much!
Ssagaji.
Cheap.
"Cheap"?
Ssagajiro.
Go shopping.
I got scared.
We can go.
Everything's all right?
One sec.
Have you put on makeup?
What if it's not okay?
You were rushing me earlier,
because I was supposedly blocking traffic.
Now you're pretending to be concerned.
All right. Let's go.
Welcome.
Impossible.
Can I help you?
No, I…
Okay.
DR IRENE:
I'M SORRY. BUT I CAN'T DO IT.
What happened?
What should I do? This is the second time.
He'll hate me.
What happened?
You didn't cancel the meeting?
It's all your fault!
What now? How will you fix it?
Hey! Your phone is ringing.
HIRO
If he was that important to you,
you would call him.
Please do it properly.
If we lose this deal, I'll be furious.
I'll be absolutely furious!
Please look.
It looks like snow.
What?
Gosh.
How beautiful.
Cedar ball!
GABRIEL BLOSSOM
Please wait here.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you very much,
that you came all the way here.
Please sit down.
I'm from Futago Sweets…
I'm Sosuke Fujiwara from Savior.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kiyomi Hosen.
You were probably expecting my mother.
I think so.
Is he here?
I'm so sorry.
My mother, who founded this place,
died.
I'm listening?
About two years ago.
She left two orders in her will.
First,
when a business partner changes the president,
call him immediately.
She had this extremely difficult test of hers.
That's why I'm so brazen
we asked to come.
Second command
I was forbidden to talk about her death
for at least three years.
Otherwise the rumors would spread quickly,
that the taste has changed or that the store has gone out of business,
even if nothing has changed.
We were told to wait three years
before we announce that she died three years ago.
If there was silence until then,
it meant we won.
Impressive.
But I'm exhausted.
I'm thinking about closing Gabriel Blossom.
I'm listening?
It's difficult, isn't it?
Taking the place of the great founder.
It seems…
fighting a battle you can't win.
A draw at best.
Perhaps
do you feel the same about the Savior now?
That's true.
But…
I guess I'm tired of life
dedicated to preserving tradition.
Sorry.
I believe the taste has changed recently
is also perfect.
I'm listening?
It's different from your mother's recipe, isn't it?
Most likely
you changed the way of extracting the aroma.
Did you notice this subtle difference?
Yes.
Compared to the original, I think
that new taste
it is richer and better.
Do you really think so?
Yes. It is also more tart.
If I had to describe it...
It tastes like spring has come.
I'm glad.
This makes me so happy.
Even though I knew it was the right move,
changing my mother's recipe
it triggered me
feeling of guilt.
It was so painful.
Maybe I'll stay a while longer
with your approach.
You had a petal in your hair.
What do you think this flower is?
What?
I tried to imitate
my mother's mischievous fun.
Of course, these are not…
cherry blossoms, right?
Most cherry blossoms have no fragrance,
so you can't get the flavor out of them.
Right.
So…
The answer is…
Apricot.
- What?
-The answer is?
Answer…
my employee will give it.
So what is it?
Well…
I guess you didn't order our liqueur,
without knowing the key ingredient?
Well, no…
I'll give you a hint.
It's on the bottle of liqueur you're holding.
Apricot.
Apricot?
You passed.
What's the name of the chocolate shop?
Which one are you opening?
Savior.
Come here.
To thank you for what you've done
Would you like to be
our first customer?
Gosh!
So they weren't cherry blossoms.
They were apricot flowers.
the taste of chocolate,
that Kenji gave me as a child,
he became for me
an unforgettable memory.
A gift of chocolate for a child
it's the greatest pleasure.
Well,
if it's not Mr. Fujiwara,
and his employee was right...
I've made my decision. You passed.
We are truly grateful.
Thank you very much!
I will also support
new traditions of the Savior.
Thank you.
I knew it would be important to take a passionate person with me
it's a good decision.
I'm glad it worked,
but thanks to you
my love life is a complete mess.
Really?
If there's anything I can do...
You can't.
But before that
I understood…
that you have an amazing gift.
You convey your true feelings.
Even though he can't look them in the eye.
Even sitting next to me, I was moved.
What?
If you are confident,
your feelings will definitely reach him.
Unless it's a ssagaji like me,
only someone good.
I wonder if I can do it.
Gobaek.
During the last session
we shared a sense of loss.
This time I want you to share
positive feelings of love.
Mr. Dear Tuna.
If you've felt love lately,
Would you like to tell us about it?
Feelings of love…
I've never felt anything like this.
What? Impossible! Really?
Poor thing.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Mr. Marumaru,
Will you be at the next session?
Of course.
Great. Me too.
Mrs. Happy Cat.
Please take this.
Chocolates can help
in starting conversations with grandchildren.
A gift of chocolate for a child
it's the greatest pleasure.
Please offer them some
during your next visit.
These are chocolates from the Savior,
in seven different flavors.
From the Savior?
Oh! If it's a problem...
Whatever. I will accept them with joy.
For the children and for me
this will definitely be a great gift.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
I'm so happy.
Gobaek.
Confession.
Sorry. Can I talk to you?
Sorry I missed it
our meeting.
I'm sorry I keep going
I'm leaving you to the wind.
I want to tell you something.
I…
For a very long time…
always…
I always liked you!
What?
What should I do?
Subtitles: Grzegorz Marczyk